testspin.com 2011-12-23

# Paid Surveys - Get paid for taking online surveys with TestSpin and earn Amazon gift certificates!

---  
TESTSPIN.COM - Privacy Policy

Revised 08/30/2009

TestSpin.com ("TestSpin", "We" or "Us") is committed to protecting each Member's privacy as outlined in this Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to TestSpin and its owner Testspin, Inc. and governs TestSpin's data collection and usage, including on TestSpin's Internet Web site (the "Site") that provides registered Members the opportunity to participate in the TestSpin Program (the "Program") and email services. This Privacy Policy explains information and privacy practices for TestSpin. It does not apply to third party providers or web sites unless otherwise stated. This Policy is effective upon acceptance of the registration for new registering Members, and is otherwise effective on August 30, 2009, for all TestSpin Members.   

**Collection and Use of Information**  
TestSpin collects a variety of both personal and non-personal information using the methods listed below and for specific purposes described below. In general, we use information collected to   

  * enable us to provide you with Program opportunities and offers that meet your preferences or for which you may qualify under criteria established by our clients;
  * facilitate activities and transactions;
  * authenticate you as a Member,
  * to operate and improve the Site, services and offerings;
  * to personalize the offerings and opportunities provided to you;
  * to fulfill your requests for participation in activities, redemption of Points, and other services; 
  * to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries; 
  * to conduct research about your use of the Program; and 
  * to offer you other products, programs, or services that may be of interest.

**Information Collected at Registration**  
To use the Program and participate in offers available through the Program you must register as a Member of the TestSpin Program. TestSpin collects personally identifiable and demographic information when you register. We require Members to give us basic contact information (such as your first name, last name and e-mail address) and demographic information (such as your zip code, age and gender). The information requested during registration may change from time to time at TestSpin's sole option. We may request additional information at the time of registration, but only information marked "required" is necessary for registration. However, the lack of information could limit or exclude you from certain opportunities you may otherwise qualify for if the information necessary to determine such qualification is not provided. Once you register with TestSpin, you will be known to Us.   
   
We do not accept registrations from persons under the age of thirteen. The Program will automatically block enrollment of any person once they indicate they are under the age of thirteen. If we discover that a user is under the age of thirteen, we will terminate the account and delete the user's information. It is the responsibility of parents and/or guardians to ensure that their children's privacy is protected and prevent children from accessing the Site. TestSpin will not be liable for any content or advertisements viewed by minor children in violation of the terms of this Policy or the Terms of Agreement ("Agreement"). 

. Our web pages also may contain web beacons. These devices automatically collect non-personal information hardware and browsing information as described below. 

A cookie is a small piece of information that a website transfers to the hard drive of a visitor's computer to facilitate communication for record-keeping purposes. Cookies contain identifying information and certain codes that assist in the recognition between your computer and our Site and speed the start-up and communication process. Cookies provide visitors a personalized experience on this Website by enabling us to determine unique preferences and trends based on visits to websites. To make full use of the Site and Services, your browser should be set to accept cookies from Us and Affiliates (clients, providers or others authorized by Us and by you by your acceptance of their invitations or links with their web sites). Affiliates utilize cookies to identify you as a Testspin User and to report your activities back to Us so we are able to credit your account with Points, redeem Points or facilitate other activities. However, your personal information specifically identified with you is not provided to Affiliates without your consent. Your personal information may be used to qualify you for participation in a survey (for example the survey may request males between 18-24 who play videogames more than 10 hours per week), but your personal identification will not be provided. You may configure your browser to not accept cookies if you desire, but you may lose some functions. 

A web beacon (or clear pixel GIF) is an invisible file located on web pages that you visit. They are often used in combination with a cookie to track navigation of a site and communicate with your computer to determine, among other things, whether you have been to that page before or viewed particular information. These commonly used counters collect no personal information, but allow us to identify unique visitors to the Site and Member visits to Affiliate's sites, and monitor activity related to each specific offer by TestSpin or an Affiliates. 

is a program that allows and supports the "Ticker" function, which is a real time on-line data stream that provides Member with both Activity invitations and links to such Activities and real time information on the Member's reward Points balance. This applet will also collect and report to Us data points from the Member's hardware, such as serial numbers for hard drives and motherboards, that provide a digital identification of the hardware. This information will be used to ensure the security and integrity of the 

Activities and the Activity responses and to verify that the Member is the person responding to the Survey. Such data will not be disclosed or sold to third parties. 

Site, the Site may automatically recognize you by one or more of the cookies. These cookies will identify you individually and enable us to identify the Activity opportunities and offers meeting your preferences or qualifications, track and record your activity on the Site and enable us to credit to, or deduct Points from, your account. This information may be added to your personal profile information and used for identifying Activity opportunities and offers relevant to your profile and preferences. These cookies also enable you to access your personal information and participate in activities, including redeeming points for merchandise or cash. 

This information may be added to your personal profile information and used for identifying Activity opportunities and offers relevant to your profile and preferences and for market research purposes   

Information obtained during your activity on the Site includes, depending on use:   

  * Your browser type (e.g., Netscape)
  * Platform-dependent information (e.g., Windows XP)
  * Requested document (the page you're looking at)
  * Referrer URL (the page you came from if within the Site)
  * Date and Time of your visit
  * Your Testspin account information
  * TestSpin Dollar conversion to RedeemItNow.com Points transaction detaill
  * Redemption of Points 
  * IP address 
  * Manner of connecting to the Internet

Additionally, for each visitor to our Site, our server may automatically recognize the following:  

  * Host origin of the request (your IP address or that of your ISP if using proxy servers)
  * Requested document (the page you're looking at)
  * Referrer URL (the page you came from if within the Site)
  * Your registered Testspin.com account information
  * Date and time of your visit

This information, sometimes called log-file or clickstream data, is used to monitor site performance, ensure the Program functions properly, and analyze traffic patterns and usage of our site. This information may be added to your personal profile and used for identifying opportunities and offers relevant to you. 

TestSpin will also capture and store requests for conversion of existing Testspin Dollars to Points. In order to verify your identity to our Affiliate RedeemItnow ("RIN") which operates the exclusive redemption store for TestSpin rewards at RedeemItNow.com and to insure only you are able to redeem Points from your account, you will be required to an accurate home address. This information will be used only for verification and not for any solicitation and will not be sold or disclosed to third parties. RIN will also capture and store your redemption transaction details which may include the items and quantities purchased, purchase price, date and time of purchase. This information is used to deduct Points for purchases and to adjust your account balance in the event of returns and exchanges and may be shared with Us. This information is also used by Us or RIN f there are any account questions or issues related to the transactions. We may also use your transaction history to make offers and opportunities available to you that match your prior interests. RIN also provides its own Privacy Policy on its web site. 

RIN also uses PayPal to provide cash award redemption for Points. The use of PayPal requires a PayPal account, which will require Users to provide PayPal with certain personal information. All use of the PayPal system is subject to the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy of PayPal, which can be accessed from the Site for from PayPal directly. 

Users may be offered other redemption opportunities through RIN, some of which may involve third party providers of merchandise. In some instances, these transactions may require the disclosure of personal information to RIN or to such third party providers, such as for example: an address for shipment of merchandise or credit card information if any additional payment is required. All use of such third party sites is subject to the Terms of Service and Privacy Policy of the third party, including the RIN Privacy Policy.   

**Additional Information Collected Via Online Surveys and Other Promotions**  
TestSpin or an Affiliate may periodically provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys, focus groups, offers, opportunities or other activities. To determine if you qualify for an offer (if there are qualification requirements) and to participate in such offers, you may need to provide additional personal information. You may decide not to accept any of the offers and you therefore can decide whether or not to disclose such information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address) and demographic information (such as gender and zip code) and personal preferences (product preferences or opinions), and may require additional or more detailed information than you have previously provided. This information to verify eligibility to participate in surveys or opportunities, to evaluate and interpret survey results, to notify you of information related to the activity, award of Points, and follow-on or additional similar offers or opportunities. 

The information we obtain from you may be supplemented with additional information from other companies. 

If we use a third party service provider to conduct TestSpin surveys or activities, that company will be prohibited from using your personal information for any other purpose. We will not share your personal information from your participation with any third party unless we give you prior notice and allow you to opt out of such sharing of information. 

**However, if you elect to participate in any activity or offers by Affiliates, either through the Site or by a link from the site to another Web site, TestSpin has no control over the collection and use of your personal information by the Affiliate. You should review the Affiliate's privacy policy to understand what information they collect and how it is used.**  

**Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**  
We do not rent or sell your personal information to anyone without your express consent or as described in this Policy. When we do share data with our Affiliates it is in aggregate form and does not identify the Member personally, unless the information is necessary to credit Points or complete redemption transactions or unless you have consented to such sharing. In general, the crediting of Points can be accomplished by only sharing your user name and not additional information. However, redemption transactions may require personal information to be shared and will require Member to provide an accurate home address for security purposes.   
   
TestSpin engages or may engage in email and direct mail marketing. Because email is an integral part of the Program and our communications with Members, you agree to receive email as part of the registration. Some email communication is necessary for us to be able to perform basic functions of the Site and Program advise you of important Program and administrative information, including changes or alterations to our Terms of Service, and thus cannot be block or stopped other than by terminating your Membership. However, you may opt-out of participation in some of the marketing programs by emailing [support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com) or my selecting the "opt-out of future emails" choice included in each marketing email.  
   
Although we house our data in the United States, it is possible that some of our data processing may occur outside of the United States. While the data protection laws of these countries may vary, we will make every reasonable effort to protect your information based upon the express terms of this Privacy Policy. By enrolling in the Program, you consent to this transfer of your personal data.   
   
**Your Access to Personal Information**  
If your personal information changes or if you want to terminate your Membership, you may correct, update, or delete it by emailing Member Services at[support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com).  
   
**Member Communications and Email**  
TestSpin will send Program and administrative emails and emails related to opportunities and offers that meet those target interests for which you have elected to receive emails. We will not send other unsolicited emails and if you receive any that you do not believe meet your criteria, you may prevent future similar emails by clicking on the opt-out links contained within each TestSpin marketing email or by sending an email to: [support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com).   
   
Members may also receive TestSpin.com program offers via telephone or postal mail. These will be offers we think you are interested in based on your criteria. However, you may opt-out of either or both of these communications by sending a request to [support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com).   
   
We may contact you in response to your inquiries, to provide services at your request and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, telephone or fax in accordance with your wishes.  
   
Because the choices you make in may not take effect immediately, it is possible you may receive a communication during the period in which your request or change is being processed.  
   
**Affiliates and 3rd Party Websites**  
   
The Site and our email may contain links to various other sites. While TestSpin makes every effort to ensure that our Affilaites post clear and complete Privacy Policies and observe appropriate data practices, these sites may have privacy policy different from that of TestSpin. The privacy practices of other websites and companies are not covered by this policy and you must review their policy to understand your rights.  
   
In some instances, TestSpin may need to validate your transaction with an Affiliate or obtain information from an Affiliate to ensure that your account is credited with the correct number of TestSpin Dollars or to complete a redemption transaction. The information shared is used solely for this purpose and may include your first name, last name, email address, mailing address or date of birth. In such instances, we will require that these third parties comply with the information practices set forth in this Privacy Promise and that the Information is not shared or used for any other purpose.  
   
**Security**  
TestSpin has established security practices to protect Member's information, including firewall security, use of encryption technology, and the use of multiple levels of password security to limit access to data to only those persons who have a need for the data.  
   
We may use contractors or vendors to help us provide some of the services at our site. If we disclose personal information for them to provide the services, it is with the requirement that the information is kept confidential and used only for those services.  
   
**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
We may amend or modify this policy from time to time. The current policy may be viewed at any time on the Site. If we make changes we believe are material, we will notify you by email so you may review the current policy.  
   
**California Privacy Rights:**  
California privacy law allows California residents to obtain specific disclosures about a business's privacy practices if it shares information with other companies for direct marketing purposes. To make a request to the TestSpin under California's privacy law, please send an e-mail to: [support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com).  
   
**Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [support@Testspin.com](mailto:support@Testspin.com) or at:   
   
Testspin.com  
Attention: Support (Privacy)  
23632 Calabasas Road, Suite 203-  
Calabasas, CA 91302
